accreditedschoolsonline.org 2019-05-08

# Accredited Schools Online's Privacy Policy

## Information We Collect

_AUTOMATIC INFORMATION:_ includes certain types of anonymous information whenever you interact with us. This anonymous data helps us improve your user experience, such as allowing us to understand how to provide more relevant and tailored content. Data includes (but is not limited to) your IP address, computer type, screen resolution, OS version, Internet browser, we also collect non-personal demographic information through the use of cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, or other similar technologies, for example, your location, educational degree, balance on mortgage, value of real estate, income, age, weight. to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status or to measure the effectiveness of e-mail communications. We may link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

By utilizing our website, you acknowledge and agree that automatic information collected may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties for the purpose of providing information about degrees, programs and other education-related products and services.

_SUBMITTED INFORMATION:_ is data that is voluntarily input and submitted by users through our web forms, which may include personal contact information, such as name, telephone number, mailing address, and email address, as well as any other information that may be required to match users to an education product or service. Submitted information is collected, stored and shared with schools and other third parties as necessary to provide users with information about education-related services, in addition to schools and programs.

By submitting this information, you authorize the Community for Accredited Online Schools (as well as our affiliated schools and partners) to contact you in accordance with all applicable laws by phone, through text messages, or by email or mail regarding education options or related topics. You also acknowledge and agree that we retain the right to release any collected information, including personally identifiable information, as needed, to businesses providing our company with administration services (such as an email delivery service). In addition, through this action, you grant us, our affiliates, and our partners and vendors the right to contact you for a period of time, and relinquish any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable law. Your submission serves as an omission to Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may exempt us from other applicable laws.

If you receive any email communications from us, a school, or third party, you will be afforded the ability to unsubscribe through a link in the email, at which point you will be removed from further mailings from that sender.

We also retain the right to release your personal information in circumstances required by law, such as to abide by a subpoena or other legal procedure. This will be when, in good faith, we believe it is necessary to preserve our rights, ensure the safety of you or others, explore alleged fraud, to reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the instance that the Community for Accredited Online Schools is merging, acquisitioning, or selling some or all of its assets to a third party.

## More About Our Use of Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user’s web browser, including for technical purposes such as web analytics. By using this website, you acknowledge that we use cookies and consent to our use of cookies. Our web analytics are primarily performed using Google Analytics, a tool provided by Google, Inc.

Advertising cookies do not contain personally identifiable information and allow users to remain anonymous. However, they do permit advertisers to make ads more relevant to the user’s interests. Advertising cookies are sometimes referred to as third-party cookies because they track navigation and publish ads on behalf of third parties. For more information about Google Analytics and its uses, check Google’s privacy policy at <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>.

The Community for Accredited Online Schools, including services and partnerships with vendors and third-party service providers, may use cookies for Web analytics such as demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis, and “lead auditing” to ensure the accuracy, relevance and validity of submitted information. In addition, our use of marketing and conversion-tracking cookies is for, but not limited to, targeting and optimizing digital ad serving to improve relevance, user experience, and advertising effectiveness.

You can remove cookies through your browser settings at any time, though you may need to do this on a per use and not one-time basis. You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.

Contact us if you have any questions or concerns about this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, or if you wish to make a Subject Access Request under the General Data Protection Regulations of the European Union.
